[Boyd] Previously, on
"From"...
Is Daddy coming home?
Any second now.
You go start saying
your prayers.
I'll be there
in a minute.
- Meagan, what are you doing?
- Maybe I can come in.
- Meagan, no!
- [Screams]
[Boyd] You want a drink, huh?
- Get the...
- No.
A man protects
his family, Frank.
Open your eyes
and look!
Look at what you did.
Look at them.
No!
Tell my parents I said goodbye.
Mom, Julie killed Norman.
- What happened to Norman?
- The monsters killed them.
There's no such thing
as monsters, honey.
Why is there a tree
in the middle of the road?
Must've gotten knocked down
in a storm or something.
Oh, this can't be
the same place.
Excuse me?
We're trying to get back onto
the highway. Could you...
- We're on the same fucking road.
- [Tires squeal]
[Moans]
Dad, I think he's bleeding.
There's something in his leg.
Are you a doctor?
I was a third-year
medical student.
Please stop.
It hurts. Ow!
- [Tires blow]
- We can make it to Colony House.
Run as fast as you can,
no matter what you see.
No matter what you hear,
you do not stop.
- Hey, I need help here!
- [Shouting]
[Ellis]
Hey. Hey! Donna, let us in!
[Gunshot]
[Victor] You're from one
of those two cars?
That hasn't happened
in a long, long time.
What do you think it means?
There are things you need to
know about where you are.
This, unfortunately, is gonna be
the worst conversation
of your life.
Do you believe
in monsters?
[Julie]
Why did you bring me here?
'Cause I wanted you
to see that if you climb
high enough, even a nightmare
can look like a dream.
- This isn't your fault.
- What do you mean?
I hear their voices.
They said it was
the only way to go home.
Sara, just tell me
what you did.
I left the door open.
- [Glass shatters]
- Those things. They walk.
They never run.
They know there's only
so many places we can go.
I feel like I'm hanging on
by a thread here.
I can't find any more bodies.
[Sobs]
- What are you looking at?
- Nothing.
[Lighter clicks]
[moaning]
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- Come on! Come on!
Open the damn door!
- [Gunshot]
- [Gasps]
[Breathes heavily]
You have a bad dream?
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
[Jade]
Tobey!
Somebody get me out of
this fucking thing. Hey!
- Tobey, where are you?
- [Woman] What's going on?
Anybody fucking... Hey.
Shut the fuck up.
People are trying to sleep.
- Who the fuck are you?
- Sorry.
I'm usually more cordial
when I do this.
[Exhales sharply]
You picked one hell of a time
to finally wake up.
Listen. I don't know
what's going on here,
alright, but you get me outta
these fucking straps
right fucking now,
or I swear to God I'm...
What?
Do you have any idea
who I am?
Oh, shit.
You're one of those.
One of what?
Okay.
Let's start
at the beginning.
[Groans]
[Exhales]
[Blinds rattle]
"Que Sera, Sera
Whatever Will Be, will Be" plays...
*FROM*
Season 01  Episode 03
Episode Title: "Choosing Day"
Aired on: March 06, 2022.
♪ When I was
just a little boy ♪
♪ I asked
my father ♪
♪ "What will
I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I
be handsome?" ♪
be rich?" ♪
♪ Here's what
he said to me ♪
♪ Que Sera Sera ♪
♪ Whatever will
be will be ♪
♪ The future's
not ours to see ♪
♪ Que Sera Sera ♪
♪ What will
be will be ♪
♪ Now I have
children of my own ♪
♪ They ask
their father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be pretty?" ♪
♪ "Will I
be rich?" ♪
♪ I tell them
tenderly ♪
♪ Que Sera Sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be
wll be ♪
♪ The future's not
ours to see ♪
♪ Que Sera Sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
[Song continues
to play]
[Clears throat]
You hungry, Frank?
Anything you need?
Look.
It's important for you
to understand that
what happens tonight...
it's not personal.
I know.
[Frank] She liked you.
Lauren.
She always liked you.
She said you were hard on people
'cause you had to be.
That you made the decisions
other people couldn't.
You're the one who was gonna
get everybody home.
[Sighs]
I wasn't always
like this, you know.
None of us were.
Look.
If there's anything
you need,
anyone
you wanna see, maybe,
tie up loose ends...
There is one thing
I'd like to do.
So, you're telling me
that right now
I'm in a town I can't leave,
and that every night
when the sun goes down,
monsters come from
the forest to hunt us?
Monsters who, incidentally,
killed my friend
the other night.
Yeah.
Fuck off.
[Laughs]
This is... this is something.
Where did he... where did he
find you?
Who?
Tobey.
Are you guys individual hires,
or is this one of
those traveling companies?
'Cause, I mean, you play
the whole thing pretty great.
I buy it.
Not him so much. I just...
I thought you were trying
a little bit too hard.
But otherwise, I...
[Laughs]
Bravo.
Oh. Money well spent.
So, uh, okay.
So, what's next?
Is there, uh...
Is there, like, some kind of
puzzle I have to solve?
Mmm.
Actually, you know what?
Never mind. Don't...
- don't spoil it for me.
- Where are you going?
Well, I'm not gonna
solve the puzzle
sitting here all day.
I'm gonna, you know,
check out the town,
turn over a few stones.
[Laughs]
Fuck. Fuckin' Tobey.
This must have cost a fortune.
You want me to keep
an eye on him?
No.
Let him wander around town
for a while.
We got enough
to deal with here.
[Indistinct chatter]
Ha.
Okay.
It's not quite
my Giacometti,
but, uh, it'll do.
Oh, perfect!
Is that for me?
Excuse me?
Hey. Do you, uh... do you have
anything motorized,
- like a scooter or something?
- What? No.
- No? Okay. This'll do.
- I...
- Thank you.
- No, that's my... Uh...
Hey, buddy.
Can I go outside today?
Oh, honey.
You need to stay in bed
a little longer.
I'm tired
of staying in bed.
And I don't like these pajamas.
They're itchy
and they don't fit right.
Oh, come on.
Your dad went to the RV
to get our stuff.
So tonight you're gonna sleep
in your own pajamas.
We all should've gone.
Well, we thought it was best
if Dad went on his own.
Well, I don't like people
going through my stuff.
Nobody's gonna do that.
Yeah, okay.
How long
are we gonna be here?
We are, uh...
we're figuring that out.
Hey. You hungry?
I saw they're making eggs.
Do you want some eggs?
Hobo eggs?
No. No, no, no.
No hobo eggs.
But they have oatmeal.
Okay.
What about you? You hungry?
Uh, no. I think I'm just
gonna go for a walk.
- Okay. Stay close.
- Yeah.
I am going to get you
your oatmeal.
Stay there.
Both speaking Cantonese...
[Plate smashes]
Oh, jeez.
You okay?
Here.
Let me get that.
One...
three...
four, five.
Berries?
I'm okay.
There's an apple tree out back
if you'd prefer that.
I see you grow
your own food.
Supermarkets around here
are terrible, so...
Oh.
[Chuckles]
You're joking.
Ellis and your dad
are gonna be back soon.
You'll feel a lot better
once you have
some of your own things.
Yeah, I guess.
Hey.
You doing okay?
No. Not really.
Come here.
All right.
Let's see
what we got here, bud.
I heard you were getting
a little itchy, so...
Thank you, Dad.
You're welcome.
Um, how did it go?
It was, uh...
it was good.
Yeah?
Are my books in there?
Oh.
Books!
How did I forget books?
Dad...
Oh, let's see.
Maybe there's one.
Maybe I can find something.
Oh, wait a minute.
We have books.
What do we want?
Do we want Adventures of
the Grand Gooligog?
Flight of the Cromenockle?
- [Gasps]
- [Tabitha] Ah. The Cromenockle.
That's my favorite.
Make the sound.
Make the sound? I have no idea
what you're even... doo-ooh!
[Giggles]
[Makes otherworldly bird noise]
[Laughs]
She doesn't sound like that.
No?
Does it sound like...
[Makes otherworldly bird noise]
No. Stop. Stop it.
Okay, okay, okay.
There's gonna be two
Cromenockles for you.
Two.
[They make
otherworldly bird noises]
[Ethan laughs]
Two Cromenockles for the cave.
- Two Cromenockles for you.
- [Laughs]
[Tabitha]
Careful with your leg.
Julie, look.
We got our stuff.
Yeah. So I see.
- Hey, come here.
- Julie!
We're reading the Cromenockle.
Julie!
[Makes otherworldly
bird noise]
- Yeah. It's really funny.
- [Donna] Hey.
Uh, sorry to interrupt.
Father Khatri is here
to talk to you about
the choosing ceremony.
What's the
choosing ceremony?
I'll let him fill you in.
All newcomers have to decide
where they're gonna live.
Here in Colony House
or down in the town.
It's just part of
how we do things here.
I'd like to take the both
of you, show you around.
Maybe take you to the house
you'd be staying in,
should you choose the town.
Well, I wanna come.
[Julie] What?
This is about all of us, right?
I wanna see.
We need you to stay here
and be with Ethan.
Donna can watch Ethan.
Okay. Fine.
You guys go ahead.
Hey.
We won't be gone long.
Okay.
[Tabitha]
You know what?
Maybe I should stay.
I shouldn't leave her alone.
I think it's very important
that both of you see this.
It's gonna be okay.
She's a tough kid.
Takes after her mother.
- [Scoffs]
- Come.
[Tires grind on gravel]
[Indistinct chatter]
[Laughs]
Good morning, everybody.
What's cooking today, huh?
[Laughs]
Is this where I find
my next clue?
Is this where the, uh...
Is this where the monsters
jump from the shadows?
Uh, "Oh, what wonders
will avail themselves
in the quaint little
roadside diner
in which my guard
hath fallen?"
Huh?
I did some summer stock
back in the day.
Not bad, right?
Oh, thank you. I'm starving.
- What've we got?
- Hey. There's a line.
Look. I'm all
for authenticity,
but I'm also
really hungry,
and since y'all basically
work for me anyways,
it's kind of okay.
Ow. What the...
Speaks Cantonese...
[Laughs]
All right. Jeez.
People really
take all this seriously.
What are you doing here?
You promised
you'd stay home.
If I didn't show up,
they would have wondered why.
It'll be okay. I wanna help.
- Sara...
- I need to help.
You should get back to the barn.
- It'll be okay.
- Sara...
I promise.
[Khatri] It's the talismans
that keep them out.
Now, there are a number of
other precautions people take.
Nailing the windows shut,
for instance.
With a child in the house,
this is a must.
Why?
Well, there'll be nights
where these... these things,
they'll try to convince you
to let them in.
And children tend to be
most susceptible.
How are people walking around
like all this is normal?
Well, the people
who survive here
are the ones who adapt.
How exactly
do they do that?
The way someone who lives
on a fault line, for example.
They adapt to the notion
that the earth
could just open up
and swallow them
at any given moment.
They go on with their lives
because that reality is a part
of the world that they live in.
Look. I wish there was
an explanation I could give you
that would make
any of this easier.
But it's gonna be fine.
Okay? Just always remember.
Place the talisman by the door.
Cover your windows.
Nail your windows shut.
You do these things, your
family's going to be just fine.
Hey. Um, I'm sorry.
What's that?
Um, we call that the box.
It's our only form
of punishment we have here.
You see, the rules we live by
are meant to protect each other,
to keep each other safe.
And when someone's
actions or negligence
leads to the death
of a resident in town,
the only punishment for that
crime is a night in the box.
Jesus.
But you keep one of those
talismans in there, right?
No.
How many times
have you used it?
Tonight will be the first.
Look. Come.
- Your house is just up ahead.
- Yeah.
[Door hinge squeaks]
So, it's not much,
but it'll keep you comfortable
if you choose to live in town.
Looks like somebody's
already living here.
Um, there was a...
There was an incident
the night before you arrived.
The first we'd had in months.
What kind of incident?
The kind that happens
when people are careless.
It was a child?
Holy fuck.
Meagan and her mother Lauren.
The father was
passed out drunk
at the other end of town
when it happened.
This is what happens
when you break the rules.
Tabitha, wait.
No, Jim, I'm sorry.
I can't.
I can't do that right now.
You make it seem like
we have a choice.
Jim.
Jim, this is
fucking insane!
That woman and her little girl
were ripped apart.
Now they're putting the dad
in some fucking box at sundown
for those things to...
You heard
what the priest said.
If he'd have followed
the rules,
they'd all still be alive
right now.
Jim? Why are you...
Why are you so eager
to take any of this
at face value, Jim?
Because I can still hear
those things whispering
outside the RV.
I can still hear them
tapping on the glass.
Tabby, whatever this is,
it's real, and we are stuck.
So we better figure out a way
to make the best of it.
'Cause we don't want to
end up like...
No, no, no. No.
[Birds chirp]
[Twig snaps]
This was Meagan's
favorite spot.
Put this swing here for her,
and she was
always wanting me
to push her higher and higher,
but... Lauren was afraid
it wasn't safe.
You'll bury me next to them,
right?
Yeah.
Of course.
Okay.
I'll just be a few minutes here.
Take whatever time you need.
All right, little guy.
Give that a try
and let me know how it feels.
Feel good?
It hurts my armpit.
Oh, it hurts your armpit?
Okay. Hold on.
Here. I'll add a little
extra padding there for you,
and if this feels good,
I'll tie it on later, okay?
Here. Try that.
Ready? Here.
Let's go
down the stairs here.
Take your time.
There you go, buddy.
Come on. Three, two, one.
Boom!
He's adorable.
Why are you doing this?
What do you mean?
You guys barely know us.
It's just what we do.
It's, like,
the ultimate escape room.
I mean, seriously, I don't know
how he pulled all this together.
So, um, I'm thinking
maybe there's a clue
in each one of the buildings?
Hmm?
Am I getting warmer?
'Cause I mean, usually,
you know,
you have some type of prompt
that lets you know
which direction to go.
But this is, uh...
This is just
some next-level shit.
Has, uh...
Has anyone
talked to you yet?
Yeah. The lady up at the, uh,
big house. Donna.
I mean, she gave me
the whole intro.
You know,
the monsters in the forest.
Tobey's dead. Blah, blah, blah.
But she didn't give me any hints
about where I'm supposed to go
next. Here's the thing, though.
Like, as thorough
as all this feels,
there's a couple flaws
in the logic.
I'm sitting here eating eggs
in a diner
in a place that's
supposed to be, what,
some kind of
mystical nightmare?
I mean,
I don't know about you,
but my nightmares
don't usually serve breakfast.
I suppose you're gonna tell me
you've got chickens
roaming around
in the big bad forest?
Yeah, but the chickens,
the cows?
We don't really know
where they come from.
Mmm.
That's actually not bad
for a nightmare breakfast.
I should probably get going.
Am I supposed to get anything
from you?
What?
I don't know. Like a clue
or some kind of
cryptic direction?
You know what? Never mind.
I'll figure it out.
Thanks.
- Was that...
- The guy from the other car.
He's gonna get himself killed.
Um, are you hungry?
Have you eaten anything yet?
No, I'm fine. I just came
to check on you guys.
Right.
[Speaks Cantonese]
Okay.
How's she doing?
Well, she's...
Uh, like I said, denial is a
major part of our family tree.
Let's see, now.
Twelve.
Ten, 12.
Okay.
- [Paper crinkles]
- [Bird chirps]
What are you doing?
I don't think you're supposed
to be out here.
Are you looking
for something?
Go away.
I can help you look.
I'm good at finding stuff.
I'm not looking.
I'm checking.
What are you checking?
You ask a lot of questions.
That was only three.
[Sighs]
- I can help you check.
- No.
No, you're trouble.
Your mom or pop comes back
and they see you out here,
who gets blamed?
And Donna cuts me off.
Then no more peaches.
- What are you talking about?
- Just go away.
Have you seen the boy
who lives out here?
What?
Forget it.
No, no. Hold on.
What do you mean
"lives out here"?
He's always walking around
out here,
and I never see him inside.
So I figured he lived
out here somewhere.
Is that right?
We're friends.
Are you, now?
Well, it's good to have friends.
Okay.
Wait. Hey, come here.
I'm checking to see
if they've moved.
If what moved?
The trees.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Did they?
Don't know yet.
I'm not done checking.
Ethan?
Ethan,
what the fuck?
Get back inside.
Mom told me to watch you.
Guess I gotta go.
Yeah.
I guess you'd better, then.
Will you let me know
about the trees?
I'll keep you looped.
Ethan, now.
[Victor]
Hey.
If you see that friend of yours,
tell him Victor says hello.
Don't talk to him.
Why?
Because he's creepy.
- No, he's not.
- Come on.
He's checking to see
if the trees moved.
Yeah, and
that's totally normal.
One, two.
[Birds chirp]
[Breathes heavily]
Yahtzee.
All right, Tobey.
Let's see what you got.
[Chuckles]
Holy shit.
[Gasps]
[Screams]
[Whimpers]
[Pants]
What the fuck?
[Gasps]
[Chuckles nervously]
Tobey, you're a fucking genius!
[Laughs]
Ah. Woo!
That's a sight
I don't see very often.
Yeah, well...
Don't get used to it.
He's not answering.
Well, perhaps you're
not listening closely enough.
I can't do it.
Frank. The box.
Can't do it.
It was never supposed...
I built the goddamn box
as a deterrent.
It's supposed
to scare people.
I... can't.
All right.
Let's say you don't.
Let's say you absolve Frank
of all his crimes.
Then what?
What happens next time?
I mean, you warned him
on several occasions.
Very publicly,
I might add.
How do you think people
are gonna react
when you let Frank go?
How much weight
do you think the rules
that hold this town together
will carry?
Aren't you supposed to be
talking to me
about the virtues of mercy?
I see.
Is that
what you'd prefer?
Hey. I'd prefer not to put
a broken man in a fucking box
to be torn apart
when the sun goes down!
That's what I'd prefer.
I'm not gonna stand here
and pretend like
this is an easy decision.
Great.
But you built a guillotine
in the town square.
What do you think happens
when people realize
you lack the conviction
to use it?
You're a terrible
fucking priest.
You know that?
Fucking worst.
Now I'm cursing
in the house of the Lord.
What the fuck is this?
[Door closes]
[Metal clanks]
[Crow caws]
Goddamn it!
[Keys jingle]
There's a little shack
about a hundred yards
beyond the tree line.
You take that,
you put it next to the door,
and you make whatever life
you can out there.
What are you gonna tell
everybody?
[Khatri]
Thank you all for coming.
Today, our newcomers will choose
where they would like
to spend their days here
with us.
Should you choose
to spend your time
with the people of the town
to live by our rules for
the good of the community
until we find our way
back home,
you will select the rock.
Should you choose to join
with the people of Colony House
to live for today because
tomorrow is not guaranteed,
you will select the flower.
Now, once you have chosen,
this choice will be final.
- Like many of us here...
- Father Khatri?
Uh, sorry.
Do you mind if I, uh...
Uh, yeah. Sure.
[Bird chirps]
Since we're all
gathered here,
figure I might as well address
the elephant in the room.
Been a lot of questions today
about Frank, the box,
the rules.
There is a fine line
between savagery
and consequence.
And if we're not willing...
Frank?
I'd like to say a few things,
if that's all right.
You know what I've been thinking
about these last couple of days,
sitting in my cell?
Christmas.
The last one me and Lauren
and Meagan had before we...
I was a good dad, you know?
I mean, I wasn't perfect,
but I wasn't like this.
That last Christmas, we got
Meagan her first dollhouse.
And when she saw it,
the look on her face...
I let this town,
those things in the woods,
I let them get
to my head, and...
I forgot what really mattered.
I... forgot that
if I'd just been
a little stronger...
there might have still been
a Christmas morning
waiting for us all
when we got home.
Don't let this place
take that away from you.
Okay?
You look after each other.
You take care of each other.
Remember what
you're living for.
I appreciate everything you're
trying to do for me, Sheriff.
No, I do. I really do.
But the only two things that I
love in this world are gone.
And I just wanna see
my girls again.
[Jade]
Wait! No! Don't go, Frank.
[Laughs]
Goddamn, I love this!
It's scary.
It's, uh, dramatic. It's...
Okay. Whoa, big fella. Okay.
All right, okay.
Easy, easy.
Easy.
Pick one.
You need to fucking let me go.
Ow! What the fuck?
Pick one!
I'm gonna fucking sue you.
Ow! Okay. All right. Okay.
- All right. All right?
- Got it.
Let's go.
Ow. Damn it! Ow! Damn! Ah!
Oh, you have no idea how badly
you just fucked up, okay?
All right? No idea.
I am gonna...
I'm gonna fucking ruin you.
All right, I'm gonna fucking
ruin all of you!
Jade, let me show
you something.
[Kenny]
Come on.
[Woman] Frank, you don't
have to do this.
You shouldn't be making
decisions like this
when you're hurting.
No. Look.
I'm the most clear-minded
I've been in a long time.
Trust me.
[Boyd]
All right.
Let's get this done.
Are you living in town
or Colony House?
Town.
[Boyd]
Sorry.
You each have to say it.
Oh, yeah. Town.
Ethan.
Town.
Okay.
Julie.
Colony House.
- What? No, no.
- No. She doesn't mean that.
Girl made her choice.
- Hold on a second.
- [Donna] It's done.
- Ceremony is over.
- No, no, I'm sorry.
She can't make that decision.
She's underage.
- No.
- Mom, it's fine.
No, it's not fine.
Come and stay with your family.
You don't have
to do that, Julie.
I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to my daughter.
Now, there's no way
anyone's gonna expect us to...
Are you gonna say something?
Okay. Everybody
just hold on, okay?
Take a breath.
Ju... Julie, Julie.
Do you want to live
in Colony House?
Yeah.
- [Scoffs]
- Why are you doing this?
She chose.
Your rules, Boyd, not mine.
No, you know what?
It's okay.
I change my mind. I go.
I choose Colony House.
- Tabitha, just...
- What?
I'm not standing here,
knowing that my daughter
- is in that fucking house.
- Everything is gonna be okay.
- No, it's not! Fucking no.
- Okay, look.
- We're gonna fix this.
- There is nothing to fix.
[shouting]
Will you shut the fuck up?
Please, please,
don't do this now, right here.
My son will be up there.
I promise you
she will be looked after.
[Khatri]
All right.
Uh, everybody,
the sun will be going down soon.
So, uh, thank you for coming.
It's okay.
I'll take care of him.
[Jade]
I'm done.
All right. Your boy,
the sheriff, crossed the line,
so just call me a car
or whatever,
'cause I'm fucking done.
Fuck.
I need you
to understand something.
No one is trying
to be cruel to you.
But you need to understand
what's going on.
Are you listening?
Did you hear what I just said?
I'm not interested.
Okay? This whole thing
lost its interest for me
the second that asshole
put his hands on me, and...
[Chuckles nervously]
[Retches]
Okay, you know what?
This isn't funny anymore.
This, uh...
You hear me, guys?
It's not funny anymore!
This, uh...
Oh, God.
I... Oh, God.
Oh, God, Jesus.
Tobey?
[Cries]
[Sobbing]
All right, come on.
[Woman] There he is.
[Onlookers murmuring]
[Ominous orchestral music plays]
[Door creaks]
You get
these people home, Sheriff.
I'll do everything I can.
Promise me?
Yeah, Frank.
I promise.
I'm ready.
[Door closes, rattles]
[Clears throat]
[Lock clanks]
Okay.
[Onlookers murmuring]
"If It Be Your Will" plays...
♪ If it be your will ♪
♪ That I speak no more ♪
♪ And my voice be still... ♪
Careful. In you go.
♪ As it was before... ♪
There's one outside.
♪ I will speak no more ♪
- ♪ I shall abide until... ♪
- Let's get you settled in.
♪ I am spoken for... ♪
- ♪ If it be your will ♪
- [Sighs]
♪ If it be your will ♪
♪ That a voice be true ♪
♪ From this broken hill ♪
♪ I will sing to you ♪
♪ All your praises
They shall ring... ♪
Speaks Cantonese...
♪ If it be your will ♪
♪ To let me sing... ♪
This is, uh...
this is Jade.
Uh, let's get you set up.
♪ If there is a choice... ♪
[Cries]
♪ Let the rivers fill ♪
♪ Let the hills rejoice... ♪
Are you and Daddy
gonna sleep in here?
Yeah, yeah.
We're all going to be together.
Is Julie
ever coming back?
Honey,
she's right up the hill.
You can see her
anytime you want.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Shall we have a read?
[Ethan] Yeah!
All right.
Last I remember,
it was chapter three.
Start from the beginning.
[Chuckles]
Yeah.
It has been a while.
♪ All your children here... ♪
Well, it all began
one sunny morning,
as a cat lay
comfortably basking in the sun,
in a beautiful green shire.
As we always do,
let's welcome
our newest family member.
Here's to Julie.
[All] To Julie!
[cheering and whooping]
Thank you.
Welcome, kiddo.
Oh, we're glad to have you.
♪ If it be your will ♪
♪ And end this night ♪
♪ Ah, ah ♪
♪ If it be your will ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, Lord ♪
♪ If it be your will ♪
[Voices whispering]
[Pants]
[Blinds rattle]
- [Voices overlapping]
- [Giggling]
[Groans]
[Whimpers]
[Screams]
[Instrumental music plays]